<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PROJECTS on German Coronel</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/</link><description>Recent content in PROJECTS on German Coronel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© German Coronel</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:49:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gecoronel.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Donde Estan App</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/donde-estan-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:49:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/donde-estan-app/</guid><description>As an engineering student, I worked in my family&amp;rsquo;s small school bus company until I graduated. Over time, I visualized different needs that parents of children transported on school buses might have. As a result of these needs, Donde Estan App was born.
Donde Estan App
● Necesity
The school transportation service in the city of Santa Fe and surroundings arises from late 1970s and early 1980s, where it has been growing year after year along with the increase in school attendance at the initial, primary and secondary levels, and It has also generated a progressive increase in the demand for the service of School transportation.</description></item><item><title>Calendar Digitizer</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/calendar-digitizer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 19:49:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/calendar-digitizer/</guid><description>Android application Calendar Digitizer applying digital image processing technologies.
● ABSTRACT
With the advancement of technology, many students have decided to start using digital calendars. However, even today important dates such as exam sessions and registration periods are only found in paper format. This document proposes the implementation of different digital image processing methods in order to obtain, from an image of a calendar with marked events, captured by a user, a list with the events by month and the days that belong to that event.</description></item><item><title>Credit Card Fraud Detector</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/credit-card-fraud-prevention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:49:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://gecoronel.github.io/project/credit-card-fraud-prevention/</guid><description>Credit card fraud detector using supervised machine learning models.
● Abstract
The task of fraud detection is not an easy issue to solve, taking into account the multiple modalities and rapid evolution that this issue has currently had. Different supervised learning techniques are proposed since they use the assumption that fraudulent patterns can be learned from an analysis of past transactions. Within the proposed techniques, it will be seen that a better prediction is achieved with a neural network model using oversampled data and weighing the minority class.</description></item></channel></rss>