<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Photoshop on German Coronel</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/designs/photoshop/</link><description>Recent content in Photoshop on German Coronel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© German Coronel</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gecoronel.github.io/designs/photoshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rappi Inc.</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/experience/rappi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gecoronel.github.io/experience/rappi/</guid><description>Rappi is a Colombian technology and on-demand delivery company headquartered in Bogotá, Colombia with main offices in São Paulo (Brazil) and Mexico City, (Mexico). The app connects users with restaurants, supermarkets, and other retailers, whose products are transported to users’ homes by delivery drivers registered on the platform It also provides other services such as RappiTravel, Rappi Bank, and Paga con Rappi.[3] Rappi was founded in 2015 by Simón Borrero, Sebastian Mejía, Felipe Villamarín.</description></item><item><title>Mercado Libre</title><link>https://gecoronel.github.io/experience/mercado-libre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gecoronel.github.io/experience/mercado-libre/</guid><description>MercadoLibre, Inc. is an Argentine company headquartered in Montevideo, Uruguay, incorporated in the United States that operates online marketplaces dedicated to e-commerce and online auctions, including mercadolibre.com. As of 2016, Mercado Libre had 174.2 million users in Latin America, making it the region&amp;rsquo;s most popular e-commerce site by number of visitors. The company has operations in Argentina, Bolivia, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, Dominican Republic, Mexico, Spain, Ecuador, Guatemala, Honduras, Peru, Panama, Uruguay, and Venezuela.</description></item></channel></rss>